[
    
    {
        "question":"Is the Booking Amount refundable?",
        "answer":"No, The booking amount is not refundable. In case of cancellations, charges would be levied."
    },
    {
        "question":"Will alcohol be served?",
        "answer":"No, alcohol will not be served on the trip, although it is not restricted and its on you."
    },
    {
        "question":"Will alcohol be served?",
        "answer":"No, alcohol will not be served on the trip, although it is not restricted and its on you."
    },
    {
        "question":"Can I board/deboard the bus from Chandigarh instead of Delhi?",
        "answer":"Yes, in both the cases, Boarding & Deboarding are allowed from Chandigarh/Delhi."
    },
    {
        "question":"If I board the bus from Chandigarh will I get a discounted price?",
        "answer":"No, one will not get a discount in such a case."
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the type of travelling bus?",
        "answer":"It will be FULL AC-Semi Sleeper Volvo bus."
    },
    {
        "question":"Is lunch included in the package?",
        "answer":"Only Breakfast and Dinner are included with the package, Lunch will not be served to anyone."
    },
    {
        "question":"Is lunch included in the package?",
        "answer":"Only Breakfast and Dinner are included with the package, Lunch will not be served to anyone."
    },
    {
        "question":"Is there any faculty going to accompany us?",
        "answer":"No."
    },
    {
        "question":"How many people will be sharing a single room?",
        "answer":"Room sharing on a Quad-Sharing bases."
    },
    {
        "question":"How many people will be sharing a single room?",
        "answer":"Room sharing on a Quad-Sharing bases."
    }
]
    
